[ED]
Hello everyone, where are we now?
Hokkaido... it's a bit of a lie, but the reason why we're here is because we're going on a national tour in the middle of summer.
The reason why we're here is because we're going on a summer tour of Japan.
The first one is here in Hokkaido. The first stop is here in Hokkaido, so we came to visit.
It was a surprise. So today, we thought we would become store clerks and do a little part time job.
We're thinking of doing a part-time job as a waiter today. Pounding! Pounding! What do you think? How is Ayamen? Yes, this is my first part-time job. But this time. I've always wanted to do a part-time job. I'm sure. I can finally do it this time.
It's a good experience. Yes, it is. I haven't had a part-time job for a long time. I wonder how we'll be exposed. Oh, no! No, you guys are going to find out. You're kidding? Really? But Ayamen. I'm confident I can blend in. Really?
But the good thing is that it's a travel bus, so you don't know what size it is.
That's great. Yes, it was good. I'm not sure I'm going to be able to do it. We'd be too obvious, so I think we should disguise ourselves lightly.
I think I'll disguise myself as a sales clerk. Yes. I brought my glasses and hat. We brought them.
They will know. Welcome. What's that? They'll know. It's too cute. That's it.
Is it bad?
Yes, very bad.
Let's try it from the bottom.
Yes, that's right.
I don't know, Ayamen, you have a distinctive voice.
What should I do?
Well, welcome.
Ayame.
What?
Welcome.
Uh...
Lower is better.
Yeah, maybe.
I'll go low.
But I'm not very friendly.
I don't like that.
I'll go low.
I'll go.
Motivation
Colorful lemonade, blue lemon soda, and café au lait
Sticker sheets for 3rd, 4th, and 5th graders
One specific sticker per drink and ice cream
Best regards
Do you have any questions?
No problem.
Yes, perfect.
Yes, please.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Dokidoki Daijunior, please take care of me.
Pleased to meet you.
Blue Lemon Soda with tea.
And a Kil-Kil-Kil Hull.
I have four kirkirhuls.
Yes, we have kirkirhulu.
Please have a blue lemon soda.
Cute.
Yay.
Here you go. The syrup is piling up, so please mix it well before you take it. Thank you very much.
Thank you for waiting.
Colorful Lemonade and Colorful Mafila Kappa.
40 grams.
This is a handy cup.
Oh no. I put too much.
Water.
Here you go.
One colorful lemonade.
One lemon soda.
One green lemon soda.
Two café au lait.
A lot.
Busy.
Green lemon soda.
Thank you for waiting. Thank you.
No problem.
Blue lemon soda.
Thank you for waiting. First, the café au lait.
One café au lait, one key chain, and one coaster.
That's all.
Here is a sticker for a special offer.
Here is a coaster and a key chain.
Thank you very much.
One berry of gelato and
One acrylic key ring
One acrylic coaster
Here is a bonus sticker and
keychain and coaster.
Thank you very much.
I'm Zerato.
I don't like the 谁谁谁谁がメチャいや telal
Thank you very much.
One berry.
That's all.
Two bonus stickers.
Iamen?
Yes, that's right.
They'll know.
Surprisingly, they don't.
That's the second one.
I got out of the iamen yesterday.
Really?
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to take off my hat and mask now.
I'm going to take it off.
I'll start the ice cafe.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
One salted milk, please.
That'll be 600 yen.
Card, please.
Yes, please.
Here you go.
One iced cafe au lait and one iced cafe au lait.
And a clear file number?
Yes, sir.
Three.
Yes, I do.
Thank you.
Here are the bonus stickers and clear files.
Iced cafe au lait, please.
Thank you very much.
I'm so thrilled.
I'm home. Good night.
Welcome home. How was it? How was it? How was it? How was it?
I was nervous. Did you do it?
Somehow. Did they know?
Yes, they knew. At first, they didn't notice me at all, but then they started to notice, and I ended up doing it like this.
What? Really?
I was nervous all the time.
I've been nervous all the time.
I've seen a lot of orders come in all at once,
Oh, they bought Mr. Umezawa's file.
Really?
I think I'll go.
I'll do my best.
Good luck.
At least, don't get caught.
Okay.
Have a good trip.
I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you.
I'm off.
I'm going home.
Please do.
Yes, ma'am.
Cafe au lait.
Here's a café au lait.
Thank you.
Milk Pudding
Bloon lemon soda.
Can I choose who gets the clear file?
You can choose who gets the clear file.
The soda is random.
One air.
How many clear files do you have?
Do you know what number?
Clear file number three.
Number three.
This is clear file number 3, sticker tape, and random air.
Okay, thank you very much.
Right this way, sir.
Café au lait.
One blue lemon soda and five acrylic cool holders.
Five.
Clear file number three, please.
Thank you very much.
Mine.
You like me?
Yes.
Really? Thank you very much.
I'm rooting for you, and I'll be at the concert.
I'll be waiting for you.
Clear file No. 3.
Thank you very much.
You're definitely an endo fan.
Yes, I'm sure.
May I?
It's not that different when it's right in front of you.
I'm so happy! It's okay! Thank you very much.
That's great! Take good care of it.
Yes, lemon soda.
Thank you.
Please.
One colorful lemonage and one acrylic tea holder.
One, yes.
With Hana Kakihara in the rear hall.
Hana Kakihara.
Thank you.
Number 3 and 11?
Number 3 and Kaki and I. Thank you very much.
This is Kaki and me clear live. Thank you.
Have a good time.
It was fun.
Mmm~! That was good.
It felt amazing!
I had a father who bought my Claire's file with the mask and glasses, but he didn't notice and said how cute it was when he got it.
I thought it was fun that he was here, but I think he did a pretty good job with the work.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you for your hard work on the job. It was fun, wasn't it?
I think there must have been about 30 people. Maybe more? It's rare to see people standing in line, and Ayomen was so busy.
He was a rookie. He was a rookie.
So we worked for an hour, and we got paid!
Earned!
How's that for a first?
Well, since we're here, since we're here...
Let's go eat something delicious in Hokkaido with the money we've just earned
What shall we eat?
We're going to enjoy what we can eat with this money!
Yes, I'm off!
We're on the move!
What is it, a shopping street?
A market?
A market!
It smells so good!
Oh, what's that? Oh, wow!
Oh, my God!
Oh, man!
I love it!
I want to go!
It's huge!
There's a place I want to go!
Here!
It's so close!
It's Donbei!
Right this way.
With our salary
How much can we eat?
Excuse me!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Two of them!
Doesn't it look so good?
Oh my God!
I heard there's a sea of pepperoni.
Two of those?
Yes, please.
I'm so happy! It's called "Karatsuki"...
I've been craving the ocean a lot lately.
Really?
I've been looking for a place to eat at the beach.
Oh, really?
I'm so happy!
This is the best place. It's in Hokkaido.
Of course.
You love the sea, don't you, Ayapan?
I love the ocean. I love it.
Yaay, it's beautiful, it's beautiful
Kimi-don S. I got 7,000 yen too
Oh, I have to work about 6 hours
I feel a bit...
Yes, excuse me, I'm Kaganzi
Thank you very much Thank you very much
Thank you very much
You're wearing a morning shirt.
Thank you very much.
Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya
Something even more amazing than I imagined came
Oh, wow!
Wow, the quality is great! It looks delicious!
It's so nice! It's our lunch!
Well then...
Can I start with the miso soup? I'd prefer to start at the beach.
Looks delicious!
Oh, wow, there's a lot of shrimp in it.
Bon appétit!
Oh, man!
Delicious!
It stings. It's too good.
It's too delicious!
I haven't had miso soup in a while.
I haven't had miso soup for a long time.
I usually don't drink soup at all.
What? What do you eat? At home.
I don't know. I don't know either.
Is that possible?
Yeah. - Oh, my God.
Oh my God, it looks so good!
Wait a minute. I'll save some for you.
Oh, I'm so nervous.
Please do.
I'll get the camera next door.
Oh, no!
It's the sea of Karatsuki.
What?
So much!
Oh, wow.
There's so much in here!
It goes deeper than you'd expect.
Yes, deep down.
There's a lot in there.
That's it!
Bon appétit!
Ta-da!
Delicious!
It's so cute!
It's too good!
Delicious!
Mellow and yammy
Mellow, mellow, mellow.
Wow.
Wow!
I'm so happy!
Good for you, keep up the good work!
I've always wanted to eat sea urchin.
It's a long time coming!
There's a lot more than I thought there would be.
Really? Thank you.
I'll have some too.
Oh, man!
I'll put a little wasabi on it.
Bon appétit! Oh, man!
It's so good!
Oh, man, it's so good!
I wish it would stay like this forever and ever!
I'm gonna miss it. I'm gonna miss it.
I had such a good time at my part-time job.
I wonder if it's okay to be so extravagant with that fun part-time job!
Okay, a reward!
Yes...
Yum! Wow!
Oh, no!
I'm so happy!
I don't want to eat sea urchin bowl! I definitely want to eat it!
There it is, right in front of me, the sea urchin milk. But I guess that's just another luxury.
Oh, no, it's gone. I noticed it was already gone too.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious. So, how was it? My first part-time job.
Well, it was a different kind of fun since I had never seen the fans in their private life.
It was a different kind of fun.
Yes, it was.
The part-time job was tough, but I managed to do it and had fun.
I'm glad we managed to do it and have fun.
Ayame was always calm.
But it's true... the fans...
You know, they came without any notice.
I didn't even give them any notice.
It's a little embarrassing, isn't it?
I'm embarrassed.
If they asked me too.
But you're all so kind.
And they're all very supportive.
I'm glad.
You said you're doing your best, so...
You're so kind
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
This travel bus will now go around
Yes, sir.
So please come on out and enjoy the goodies.
We've got some cool photo ops.
Oh, yeah.
And we have ice cream.
And drinks
Yes, we have a lot of stuff.
We have a lot of drinks.
Yes, sir.
We hope you enjoy the tour and the travel bus as well.
And that's the end of our Hokkaido trip. Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button.
We'll see your comments.
Bye bye!